Love is a game where everyone gets hurt.
الحب لعبة حيث يتعرض الجميع للأذى.
You let your guard down,
لقد خفضت حذرك،
get played, then betrayed.
يتم اللعب بها، ثم يتم خيانتها.
And in the end, it's over, just like hitting reset.
وفي النهاية، انتهى الأمر، تمامًا مثل إعادة الضبط.
That's why I'll never get involved.
لهذا السبب لن أتدخل أبدًا.
I swore I'd live by that rule...
لقد أقسمت أنني سأعيش وفقًا لهذه القاعدة...
But yesterday, with this man...
لكن بالأمس، مع هذا الرجل...
Game start.
بداية اللعبة.
"Therapy Game" (Episode 1)
"لعبة العلاج" (الحلقة 1)
What did he mean by having someone he wanted to introduce me to?
ماذا يعني عندما قال أنه يريد أن يقدمني إلى شخص ما؟
And a college guy younger than me?
وشاب جامعي أصغر مني؟
Are you kidding me?
هل تمزح معي؟
Did he really have to ask me...?
هل كان عليه حقا أن يسألني...؟
Of course he did.
بالطبع فعل ذلك.
Huh?
هاه؟
You always say that,
أنت تقول ذلك دائمًا،
but when have you not completely messed up Itsuki-chan's love life?
لكن متى لم تفسد حياة إيتسوكي تشان العاطفية بالكامل؟
It's about time you grew out of that brother complex.
لقد حان الوقت للتخلص من عقدة الأخوة تلك.
Minato-chan, are you ready?
ميناتو-تشان، هل أنت مستعد؟
Isn't it almost time?
أليس الوقت قد حان تقريبا؟
Oh...
أوه...
You're right.
أنت على حق.
I'm heading out then.
سأخرج إذن.
I'm just worried because we're brothers.
أنا قلق فقط لأننا إخوة.
But...
لكن...
you can't go sabotaging things, you hear?
لا يمكنك تخريب الأشياء، هل تسمع؟
I know.
أنا أعرف.
Ooh.
أوه.
This is my younger brother, Minato.
هذا أخي الأصغر ميناتو.
He's a freelance photographer.
إنه مصور مستقل.
He takes really good photos.
إنه يلتقط صورًا جيدة حقًا.
Oh.
أوه.
That's amazing!
هذا مدهش!
My brother just takes blurry photos with his phone.
أخي يلتقط صورًا ضبابية بهاتفه فقط.
Huh?
هاه؟
Don't compare me to an amateur.
لا تقارنني بالهواة.
Minato.
ميناتو.
Sorry!
آسف!
You have a point...
لديك وجهة نظر...
It's like comparing a lion to a house cat...
إنه مثل مقارنة الأسد بقطة منزلية...
Hmm?
همم؟
Am I wrong?
هل انا مخطئ؟
Ah, the delivery's here...
اه، التسليم هنا...
Wait here for a sec, okay?
انتظر هنا لمدة ثانية، حسنًا؟
Um...
واحد...
I'm just going to use the restroom.
سأستخدم الحمام فقط.
Hey, let me ask you something.
مهلا، دعني أسألك شيئا.
Did you know that guy used to
هل تعلم أن هذا الرجل كان
have a really shady job?
هل لديك وظيفة مظللة حقًا؟
What?
ماذا؟
Shady, you say...?
شادي، كما تقول...؟
Come here for a second.
تعال هنا لثانية واحدة.
No...
لا...
I'd rather not.
أفضل أن لا أفعل ذلك.
Didn't you hear me? I said come here.
ألم تسمعني؟ قلت تعال هنا.
You want to know, don't you?
تريد أن تعرف، أليس كذلك؟
The kind of work he did was...
وكان نوع العمل الذي قام به...
I'll accept all of it!
سأقبل كل ذلك!
If he were still doing it now, I would absolutely stop him...
لو كان لا يزال يفعل ذلك الآن، سأوقفه بالتأكيد...
No matter what kind of past Itsuki-san has,
بغض النظر عن نوع الماضي الذي يمتلكه إيتسوكي سان،
I will accept him for who he is.
سأقبله كما هو.
What an idiot.
يا له من أحمق!
Minato?
ميناتو؟
This is boring. I'm leaving.
هذا ممل. سأرحل.
It's not that I hate you...
ليس أنني أكرهك...
But...
لكن...
I've fallen for Yusuke.
لقد وقعت في حب يوسوكي.
I want to be with him.
أريد أن أكون معه.
I'm so sorry!
أنا آسف جدا!
I'm sorry, I didn't realize.
أنا آسف، لم أكن أدرك ذلك.
Yuka, you were suffering so much,
يوكا، لقد كنت تعاني كثيرًا،
and I didn't notice a thing...
ولم ألاحظ شيئا...
Right now...
الآن...
I can't think straight...
لا أستطيع التفكير بشكل سليم...
Shizuma...
شيزوما...
- Hey, he just turned and left... - He must be unwilling to accept it...
- مهلا، لقد استدار وذهب للتو... - لا بد أنه غير راغب في قبول ذلك...
(Veterinary School Veterinary Surgery Lab)
( مختبر جراحة الطب البيطري بكلية الطب البيطري)
That guy...
هذا الرجل...
Did something happen to him?
هل حدث له شيء؟
I heard he got dumped.
سمعت أنه تم التخلي عنه.
What?
ماذا؟
Yuka broke up with him?
يوكا انفصلت عنه؟
I heard she cheated on him.
سمعت أنها خانته.
That's harsh...
هذا قاسي...
At a time like this,
في وقت كهذا،
is where I come in.
هذا هو المكان الذي أتدخل فيه.
Hey, Shizuma.
مهلا، شيزوما.
I'm here for you tonight!
أنا هنا من أجلك الليلة!
Let's drink our sorrows away
دعونا نشرب أحزاننا بعيدا
and forget all about Yuka!
وانسي كل شيء عن يوكا!
It's really not a big deal.
إنها ليست مشكلة كبيرة حقا.
As long as Yuka is happy...
طالما أن يوكا سعيدة...
What's there to be depressed about?
ما الذي قد يجعلك مكتئبا؟
In this day and age, one in every three men
في هذا العصر، واحد من كل ثلاثة رجال
will be single for life.
سوف أكون عازبا مدى الحياة.
For life...
من أجل الحياة...
About Shizuma...
بخصوص شيزوما...
Did you forget what a handful he is when he's drunk?
هل نسيت كم هو صعب المراس عندما يكون في حالة سكر؟
Ah...
اه...
But jackals mate for life...
لكن الذئاب تتزاوج مدى الحياة...
I'm...
أنا أكون...
heading out...
متجه للخارج...
You're coming too.
أنت قادم أيضا.
Look at you.
أنظر إليك.
Is Itsuki-chan's new partner a good kid?
هل شريكة إيتسوكي تشان الجديدة طفلة جيدة؟
Yeah.
نعم.
- I mean, a guy like a puppy... - That's pretty rare.
- أعني، رجل مثل الجرو... - هذا نادر جدًا.
Right?
يمين؟
My brother always used to date weirdos.
كان أخي دائمًا يواعد أشخاصًا غريبين.
I thought this time would be the same...
اعتقدت أن هذه المرة ستكون هي نفسها...
Then...
ثم...
it's time for Minato-chan to graduate from his brother complex.
لقد حان الوقت لتخرج ميناتو تشان من عقدة أخيه.
Even if you're brothers, you can't be joined at the hip forever.
حتى لو كنتم أخوة، لا يمكنكم أن تظلوا مرتبطين إلى الأبد.
I know... I know, but...
أنا أعلم... أنا أعلم، ولكن...
I can't help but worry...
لا أستطيع إلا أن أشعر بالقلق...
I get it.
أحصل عليه.
That feeling...
هذا الشعور...
I get it!
أحصل عليه!
Huh?
هاه؟
I have a younger brother too.
عندي أخ أصغر أيضاً.
That feeling of worry,
هذا الشعور بالقلق،
I know it all too well.
أنا أعرف كل ذلك جيدا.
He's the type to wag his tail and follow anyone.
إنه من النوع الذي يهز ذيله ويتبع أي شخص.
It makes me so worried.
إنه يجعلني أشعر بالقلق الشديد.
Well, well, young man.
حسنًا، حسنًا، أيها الشاب.
You're finally awake?
هل استيقظت أخيرا؟
You've got some nerve talking to Minato-chan.
لقد حصلت على بعض الشجاعة في التحدث مع ميناتو تشان.
Mama-san.
حماة " أم الزوج أو أم الزوجة.
Hey, you guys.
مرحبا يا شباب.
Your friend is awake!
صديقك مستيقظ!
Oh, you're awake?
أوه، هل أنت مستيقظ؟
Shizuma.
شيزوما.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Yeah.
نعم.
I'm fine~
انا بخير~
Really?
حقًا؟
Should I put your drink on the table for you?
هل يجب أن أضع لك مشروبك على الطاولة؟
Oh, I'll get it.
أوه، سأحصل عليه.
Hey.
يا.
- We weren't done talking about leopard cats! - I'm sick of hearing about it.
- لم ننتهي من الحديث عن قطط النمر! - لقد سئمت من سماع ذلك.
Aren't you worried?
ألا تشعر بالقلق؟
They're so cute.
إنهم لطيفين للغاية.
- If they go extinct, we'll never see them again! - I get it... I get it.
- إذا انقرضت فلن نراها مرة أخرى! - فهمت... فهمت.
Geez, Tatsumi is such a bad drunk...
يا إلهي، تاتسومي هو حقا سكير سيء...
Don't worry about me.
لا تقلق علي.
Go listen to Tatsumi.
اذهب واستمع إلى تاتسومي.
Huh? Okay, then...
هاه؟ حسنًا إذن...
I'll let you know when we're leaving.
سأخبرك عندما نغادر.
Wouldn't it be better to have him take you home?
أليس من الأفضل أن يأخذك إلى المنزل؟
You're even worried about me.
حتى أنك قلق علي.
You're such a good little brother.
أنت أخ صغير جيد جدًا.
Yeah.
نعم.
There's no need to get over your brother complex!
لا داعي للتغلب على عقدة الأخوة لديك!
None at all!
لا شيء على الإطلاق!
Hey, kid.
مهلا يا صغيري.
Don't spoil this one too much.
لا تفسد هذا الأمر كثيرًا.
No, he's perfect just the way he is.
لا، فهو مثالي كما هو.
Hey!
يا!
We're not even family.
نحن لسنا حتى عائلة.
I hate guys like this who don't know their boundaries.
أنا أكره هؤلاء الرجال الذين لا يعرفون حدودهم.
But...
لكن...
This guy here...
هذا الرجل هنا...
I heard his girlfriend dumped him.
سمعت أن صديقته تركته.
I see.
أرى.
She cheated on me without me even knowing...
لقد خانتني دون أن أعرف...
She said she liked the new guy more...
قالت أنها تحب الرجل الجديد أكثر...
and so she left me.
وهكذا تركتني.
See?
يرى؟
This guy too.
وهذا الرجل أيضا.
This is why love only leads to pain.
لهذا السبب الحب لا يؤدي إلا إلى الألم.
If you're so unwilling to accept it,
إذا كنت غير راغب في قبول ذلك،
you should get revenge.
ينبغي عليك الانتقام.
Make her feel the same pain.
جعلها تشعر بنفس الألم.
I am unwilling to accept it.
أنا غير راغب في قبول ذلك.
But even so,
ولكن مع ذلك،
there's no point in hurting her.
لا فائدة من أذيتها.
She chose to end things this way.
لقد اختارت أن تنهي الأمور بهذه الطريقة.
I'd be more upset if she wasn't happier now than she was with me.
سوف أكون أكثر انزعاجًا إذا لم تكن أكثر سعادة الآن مما كانت عليه معي.
But...
لكن...
It's too scary... I don't think I can ever fall in love again...
إنه أمر مخيف للغاية... لا أعتقد أنني سأتمكن من الوقوع في الحب مرة أخرى...
Someone like you...
شخص مثلك...
deserves to be happy.
يستحق أن يكون سعيدا.
That's the first time anyone's ever said that to me.
هذه هي المرة الأولى التي يقول لي فيها أي شخص ذلك.
Aren't you in a bad mood today too?
هل أنت في مزاج سيء اليوم أيضًا؟
Let's just drink our sorrows away.
دعونا نشرب أحزاننا بعيدًا.
I never thought I'd make a move on a straight guy...
لم أكن أتوقع أبدًا أن أتحرك نحو رجل مستقيم...
Until...
حتى...
Shizuma.
شيزوما.
Watch where you're going!
انتبه إلى المكان الذي تذهب إليه!
You're a big guy, you're heavy!
أنت رجل كبير، أنت ثقيل!
Mmm.
ممم.
Human's body heat is so warm~
حرارة جسم الإنسان دافئة جدًا~
Geez, where did your friends go?
يا إلهي، أين ذهب أصدقاؤك؟
Whoa!
واو!
Want to rest for a bit before we keep going?
هل تريد أن تستريح قليلاً قبل أن نستمر؟
You're in no shape to get home like this.
أنت لست في وضع يسمح لك بالعودة إلى المنزل بهذه الطريقة.
Mmm.
ممم.
And I can't just leave you here by yourself.
ولا أستطيع أن أتركك هنا بمفردك.
Thank you...
شكرًا لك...
Minato.
ميناتو.
Feeling better?
هل تشعر بتحسن؟
Yeah.
نعم.
What about you, Minato?
ماذا عنك ميناتو؟
Are you all right now?
هل انت بخير الان؟
My wounds are different from yours.
جروحي تختلف عن جروحكم.
Someone stole my precious brother from me.
لقد سرق أحدهم أخي الثمين مني.
Then...
ثم...
I'll take your brother's place.
سأحل محل أخيك.
Wait...
انتظر...
You're getting a little too handsy.
أنت تتصرف بعنف شديد.
You don't like it?
هل لا يعجبك ذلك؟
I thought you were enjoying it.
اعتقدت أنك تستمتع به.
Huh? Why would I be enjoying it?
هاه؟ لماذا سأستمتع به؟
Because...
لأن...
Even though you say that,
على الرغم من أنك تقول ذلك،
you didn't pull away.
لم تبتعد.
It's okay to be honest and lean on me.
لا بأس أن تكون صادقًا وتعتمد علي.
I told you...
أخبرتك...
You're drunk.
أنت سكران.
Hey.
يا.
Minato.
ميناتو.
I thought, "I've finally found the one."
فكرت، "لقد وجدت الشخص المناسب أخيرا".
It's not really like me,
إنه ليس مثلي حقًا،
but...
لكن...
Yuka...
يوكا...
The alarm.
المنبه.
Shizuma, I'm not Yuka.
شيزوما، أنا لست يوكا.
I'm...
أنا أكون...
Minato.
ميناتو.
Huh?
هاه؟
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Hmm?
همم؟
Don't tell me...
لا تخبرني...
You don't remember me?
ألا تتذكرني؟
Sorry.
آسف.
I don't remember a thing.
لا أتذكر شيئا.
I see...
أرى...
You were black-out drunk yesterday.
لقد كنت في حالة سكر شديد أمس.
It's no wonder you can't remember.
ليس من المستغرب أنك لا تستطيع التذكر.
Hey! What are you doing?
مهلا! ماذا تفعل؟
- Untie me! - But...
- أطلقني! - لكن...
What you did to me...
ماذا فعلت بي...
I'm not going to let you pretend it never happened.
لن أسمح لك بالتظاهر بأن هذا لم يحدث أبدًا.
Hey! What do you think you're doing?
مهلا! ماذا تعتقد أنك تفعل؟
Untie me, now!
أطلقني الآن!
Since you're so gentle,
لأنك لطيف جدًا،
you wouldn't break something precious to me, would you?
لن تكسر شيئًا ثمينًا بالنسبة لي، أليس كذلك؟
I thought if we did the same thing as yesterday, you might remember.
اعتقدت أنه إذا فعلنا نفس الشيء كما فعلنا بالأمس، فقد تتذكر.
This is useless!
هذا لا فائدة منه!
Let me go!
دعني أذهب!
Then what will it take for you to remember?
إذن ما الذي سيتطلبه الأمر حتى تتذكر؟
Tell me.
أخبرني.
Who was it that brought you here when you were completely wasted?
من الذي أتى بك إلى هنا عندما كنت مرهقًا تمامًا؟
What's my name?
ما هو اسمي؟
You're the one who came on to me first.
أنت الشخص الذي جاء إلي أولاً.
And now you're acting like you don't know me.
والآن تتصرف وكأنك لا تعرفني.
You're the worst.
أنت الأسوأ.
I think you have a point.
أعتقد أن لديك وجهة نظر.
But I can't just accept being treated like this.
لكن لا يمكنني أن أقبل أن يتم التعامل معي بهذه الطريقة.
- Let's talk this out... - No.
- دعنا نتحدث في هذا الأمر... - لا.
If you feel bad, then just lie back and take it.
إذا كنت تشعر بالسوء، فقط استلقِ وتحمل الأمر.
I can't.
لا أستطبع.
Why?
لماذا؟
I'll make you feel good.
سأجعلك تشعر بالسعادة.
I didn't ask you to!
لم اطلب منك ذلك!
Just lie still.
فقط استلقي ساكنا.
Stop it!
اوقفها!
I won't.
أنا لن.
I told you to stop, didn't you hear me?
لقد طلبت منك التوقف، ألم تسمعني؟
Wait!
انتظر!
Shizuma, that hurts!
شيزوما، هذا يؤلمني!
Will you listen to me now?
هل ستستمع لي الآن؟
I'll listen...
سأستمع...
I'll listen!
سأستمع!
Just untie me first!
فقط قم بفك قيدي أولا!
Damn it. I should've tied your feet too.
يا إلهي، كان يجب عليّ أن أربط قدميك أيضًا.
Are you always this forceful?
هل أنت دائما بهذه القوة؟
So what if I am?
فماذا لو كنت كذلك؟
If you're always this aggressive,
إذا كنت دائمًا بهذا القدر من العدوانية،
you'll never win anyone over.
لن تتمكن من كسب ثقة أي شخص أبدًا.
You'll be alone forever.
سوف تكون وحيدا إلى الأبد.
What?
ماذا؟
This is edited so beautifully.
لقد تم تحريره بشكل جميل.
It looks professional.
يبدو احترافيا.
Oh my, everyone's photos are so pretty.
يا إلهي، صور الجميع جميلة جدًا.
- Mama-san, yours is the best. - Hanako looks gorgeous.
- ماما سان، أنت الأفضل. - هاناكو تبدو رائعة.
Isn't this a little over-edited?
أليس هذا مبالغا فيه قليلا؟
What is it?
ما هذا؟
It's so beautiful.
إنه جميل جداً.
He said he doesn't remember a thing.
قال أنه لا يتذكر شيئا.
- Are you kidding me? - You're still on about that?
- هل أنت تمزح معي؟ - هل مازلت تتحدث عن هذا؟
Don't I always say you should just move on?
هل أقول دائمًا أنه يجب عليك المضي قدمًا؟
A heartbroken straight guy...
رجل مستقيم القلب مكسور...
Just forget about him.
فقط أنسي أمره.
Does this mean I got dumped?
هل هذا يعني أنني تركت؟
It's okay to be honest and lean on me.
لا بأس أن تكون صادقًا وتعتمد علي.
No...
لا...
He may have been drunk, but he was the one who made the first move.
ربما كان مخمورا، لكنه كان هو الذي قام بالخطوة الأولى.
He may be straight,
قد يكون مستقيما،
but that guy definitely has potential.
لكن هذا الرجل لديه إمكانات بالتأكيد.
Besides, when a man is heartbroken, that's the perfect time to make your move, isn't it?
وبالإضافة إلى ذلك، عندما يكون الرجل حزينًا، فهذا هو الوقت المثالي للتحرك، أليس كذلك؟
Hanako!
هاناكو!
Then how about we make a bet?
إذن ماذا عن أن نراهن؟
If Mr. Minato can win over that straight guy,
إذا استطاع السيد ميناتو الفوز بهذا الرجل المستقيم،
I'll shave my head.
سأحلق رأسي.
Honestly, you guys.
بصراحة يا شباب.
Stop egging him on!
توقف عن تحريضه!
Fine. I'll show you.
حسناً سأريك.
I'll mend his broken heart,
سأصلح قلبه المكسور
and then I'll dump him hard!
وبعد ذلك سأتخلص منه بقوة!
In that case, Minato-chan,
في هذه الحالة، ميناتو-تشان،
I'd like you to run an errand for me.
أريد منك أن تقوم بمهمة بالنسبة لي.
This...
هذا...
Could you deliver this for me?
هل بإمكانك توصيل هذا لي؟
Huh?
هاه؟
Mama-san, why are you making him go?
ماما سان، لماذا تجعلينه يذهب؟
To see that kid so fixated on someone besides Itsuki-chan...
أن ترى هذا الطفل مهووسًا بشخص ما إلى جانب إيتسوكي تشان...
It's really quite a sight.
إنه مشهد جميل حقا.
My mission in this game...
مهمتي في هذه اللعبة...
is to make this guy fall for me and then dump him.
هو أن أجعل هذا الرجل يقع في حبي ثم أتركه.
There's no way I'm going to let him hurt me and get away with it.
لا توجد طريقة تجعلني أسمح له بإيذائي والإفلات من العقاب.
Just wait until I crush you under my heel.
فقط انتظر حتى أسحقك تحت كعبي.
(Next Episode Preview) First, I'll lead you on.
(معاينة الحلقة القادمة) أولاً، سأقودك إلى الموضوع التالي.
What on earth happened?
ماذا حدث على الأرض؟
If rumors spread that you got dumped by a woman,
إذا انتشرت شائعات بأنك تركت من قبل امرأة،
and then started dating a man, what would you do about the gossip?
وبعد ذلك بدأت في مواعدة رجل، ماذا ستفعل بشأن هذه الشائعات؟
The boundaries Shizuma can accept...
الحدود التي يمكن أن تقبلها شيزوما...
I'll figure them out for you.
سأكتشف ذلك لك.
Towards a man...
نحو رجل...
What if I'm feeling my heart race for him like never before?
ماذا لو كنت أشعر أن قلبي ينبض تجاهه أكثر من أي وقت مضى؟